<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nam Nguyen Hoai</title>
    <link>https://namnh68.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nam Nguyen Hoai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 23:31:41 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://namnh68.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 23:31:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/test/</guid>
      <description>Nguyễn Hoài Nam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CICD in OpenStack</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/cicd-in-openstack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 20:40:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/cicd-in-openstack/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack is a platform to build private and public cloud, it includes so many projects to do this,each project has its function. For example: Neutron is to provide network as a service, Nove is to provide compute as a service, etc. There is a large OpenStack community including developers and users to support it like developing new features. So one a big question is that how to verity source code from developers to make sure the source code is already for production.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install OpenStack AIO via Kolla-ansible</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-openstack-aio-via-kolla-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 11:43:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-openstack-aio-via-kolla-ansible/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This article is my note during installing OpenStack AIO via Kolla-ansible.
Topology We will use two nodes. One is for OpenStack, one is for Kolla-ansible which will be used to install OpenStack to the OpenStack node.
Installing Step 1: Prepare environment  Networking: You need to setup two nodes with two interfaces as the above topology. Kolla-ansible node with connect to OpenStack node via management network. OpenStack node will be configured to get public network as provider network in OpenStack system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Jenkins on CentOS 7</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-jenkins-on-centos-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 20:36:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-jenkins-on-centos-7/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This article is to guide how to setup Jenkins on CentOS 7. All below commands will be run with root privilege.
Installing Step 1: Update CentOS 7 system  You need to update your system to get lastes stable packages, then reboot.  yum install epel-release -y yum update reboot   Stop SeLinux   Step 2: Install Java 1.8  Before you can install Jenkins, you need to setup a Java virtual machine on your system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Jenkins on Ubuntu 16.04</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-jenkins-on-ubuntu-16.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 23:41:46 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/2018/10/install-jenkins-on-ubuntu-16.04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This guide is to install Jenkins on Ubuntu 16.04. Please make sure that your system already was updated and running commands with root privilege.
Installing Step 1: Install Java OpenJDK 8 sudo apt update sudo apt install python-software-properties apt-transport-https -y sudo add-apt-repository ppa:openjdk-r/ppa sudo apt update sudo apt install openjdk-8-jdk -y  Verify Java after installing
java -version  The command should be have a result like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://namnh68.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://namnh68.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Yeah, I am Nam Nguyen Hoai</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>